Elizer A. Bachanicha Jr.

I have more than two years of experience developing web applications, mainly using .Net Core as Back-end, Vue 2+ for front-end and MySql for data storage.

Have a teachable spirit and always open to learn new things, development trend, and especially on development standard.



Full-stack Web developer

https://bachelizer.github.io/

Email: bachanichaelizer@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/elizer-bachanicha-050027224

GitHub: https://github.com/bachelizer/

Mobile No. +639187714627 / +639455923183

HTML

CSS

Javascript































Bootstrap, .Net Core , Vue, Javascript, Vuetify, Mysql, FastReport, Dapper ORM, Typescript, Git versioning control, Github

laravel, React, Firebase, Tailwind CSS

Work Experience

Full Stack Web Developer (Full-time)

2020 - Present

Agusan del Sur State College of Agriculture and Technology

Duties and Responsibilities

Develop College web applications, maintain, and continuous engagement with the end-user for maintenance and system enhancement.

Front-end Developer (Part-time)

February 2022 – July 2022 ZEA Informatique Inc.

Duties and Responsibilities

Develop Front-end using Vue.js, and Vuetify with Firebase Backend

IT Specialist (Full-time)

2018 - 2020

Bayugan City Doctors Hospital

Duties and Responsibilities

System Administration, Software, Hardware, and Network Troubleshooting, Graphic Designing

Education

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology 2018

Agusan del Sur State College of Agriculture and Technology San Teodoro, Bunawan, Agusan del Sur, Philippines